# **Harriet Bradley**

07507620991
harrietbradley96@gmail.com
Harriet\_Bradley
https://www.linkedin.com/in/harriet-bradley-2070b1122/
101 Sandringham Road, E8 2LL

### About me

Having worked in agencies of varied size and stature, I'm well-versed in working with clients of every level, such as Peperami, Homebase, Ford and Tesco. As you can imagine, each business has their own unique challenges, and I've loved helping them figure out how to overcome them.

I am a firm believer that having an open mind and a willingness to learn is what makes a good strategist. I really enjoy collaborative working and blue skies thinking. The way we communicate is changing so quickly that I believe being able to figure out a way to do so authentically comes from being able to see things from different POVs.

# **Experience**

### BBH London, 2022- Present

At BBH I work mainly on the Tesco account; focusing on quality brand campaigns such as Food Love Stories, as well as their reputation work and CX business - more commonly known as Clubcard. Additionally I've been involved with an ethnographic research project on high-net-worth individuals and the luxury market for Audi.

## VMLY&R London London, 2021- 2022

At VMLY&R I worked on the CX team closely with the head of strategy and the client themselves (Ford). My key responsibilities included research and development, rationalised planning, planning and facilitating workshops and conducting testing of new concepts pre and post market launch.

# Atomic London London, 2019 - 2020

I worked on a variety of accounts including Peperami, Homebase and Greater Anglia. I managed Atomic's internal brand optimisation platform called Brand Shapes, as well as contributing to cultural research across all clients.

### **Jaywing**

## Leeds, August - October 2018

Working in accounts as an exec, it was my job to oversee a range of clients, working across the strategy and creative departments.

#### \*References available upon request

#### Education

### **Leeds Arts University**

Creative Advertising BA Hons 2:1

#### The Manchester College

Costume and Fashion production Foundation - Merit

#### Skills

Brand strategy

Comms strategy

CX strategy

Data interpretation

Copywriting

Pitching

Research & Development

Social Media

#### **Software Skills**

OnePulse

**Awario** 

**Brand Watch** 

Alexa Marketing

Microsoft Office

Adobe

Keynote

Mural